Mihaela Younas

London, CR0 7BB | +44 7496590582 | Github | LinkedIn | Resume and Projects

Junior Web Developer

Full-Stack Software Web Development Student, with 9+ years Managerial and Administrative experience in the Retail Sector, and co-founder of E-Commerce store and platform, Rex Gadgets.

Strong proficiency and understanding of developing Web Applications written in Python, JavaScript, HTML and CSS, while having strong proven skills in Leadership and Team Productivity while working as Manager. Searching for entry-level Software Development opportunities, including Junior Front-End (and/or JavaScript) Developer to further implement my Development skills within an innovative, commercial setting.

Technical Skills

Skills Achieved	Developing Skills	Core Skills
Python	JavaScript-Testing	Organised
JavaScript	API's	Good Communication
Cascading Style Sheets(CSS)	J-Query	Problem Solving
HTML	Flask	Teamwork
Product Research	Databases	Working within the deadline
Bootstrap	Jest	Agile Environment
Design Thinking		

Relevant Qualifications

Full-Stack Software Web Development Diploma- (E-Commerce Applications)

Code Institute

Feb 2022 - Present

Technological Areas: Python, JavaScript, CSS, Flask, HTML, J-Query, Jest, Database, API

Technical Projects

My Virtual Doctor - Github | Demo

My Virtual Doctor is an appointment system to help patients and admins with appointment booking or managing.

- Built in pure Python logic.
- Handling all the input errors and returning valid information for the user.
- Worked with saving all the data into the google spreadsheets.

Brain Wizzz - Github | Demo

Brain Wizz is a memory game that challenges people with visual memory in order to match two cards to clear the board.

• Utilised Javascript logic for interactivity .

- Handling user events and changing DOM elements to deliver an interactive user interface.
- Combined HTML and CSS knowledge to build a fully responsive website.

Rex Removals - Github | Demo

Rex Removals is a website made to help people to connect to a company specialised in moving furniture and helping people move their houses ,also providing the best customer service.

- Applied all my new skills to present a fully responsive website for an imagined business.
- Presenting four separate pages, styled and responsive .

Love Sandwiches - Github | Demo

Love Sandwiches is a walkthrough project app which is fully based on **Python** and collects data from the user and returns it in a spreadsheet and stores it.

• Utilised the skills I have achieved by studying Python logic .

More projects to be seen on Github

Experience

Co-founder Rex Gadgets (E-commerce)

September 2019-Present

Establishing from scratch an E-Commerce site with partner, reached 700+ orders per month, and generating traffic for over 1000 of clients. Managing 10000 pieces stock of Mobile accessories.

- Researching products that sell best ,researching prices and optimising SEO.Researched mobile accessories best sellers and introducing key words for high ranking .
- Negotiating with suppliers and ordering large wholesale orders .Needed price negotiation for the product itself ,shipping, shipping and customs as it was coming from China, also type of shipping(by boat,train or plane)
- Offering high quality customer service by replying to messages and concerns, returns and exchanges.
- Managing multiple accounts at the same time . Managed 4 + accounts.
- Managed large stock amounts of over 10.000 pieces of iPhone cases , kept them in boxes and wrote on each box the colours and model .
- Also developed our own brand for MMA equipment with a company overseas. Created the products but stopped the production because of quality reasons.

Nails Technician - Angels Salon

october 2018 -december 2018

- Respond to customer requests and concerns in a timely manner.
- Prepared nail beds and cuticles, shaped nails and applied polish for multiple daily customers.

Manager Firezza Wandsworth

January 2017

- Applied expertise in team leadership to address productivity and performance issues, making weekly reports and meetings with the staff.
- Managed staffing schedules for high numbers of employees, delivering operational efficiency whilst remaining under budget, by avoiding having extra staff when not busy. Managing 10-15 employees.
- •Communicated daily performance and productivity expectations to high-volume teams, motivating them effectively. They would be getting a bonus from the area manager before holidays, I would discuss every end of the day our performance and what we can do to improve.
- Developed strong teams by skillfully recruiting, orienting and training loyal, hard-working employees. After posting
 recruiting ads, or just getting their requests I would contact the candidates by phone and arrange face-to-face
 interviews.
- Assessed employee performance through careful monitoring and development programmes, leading to promoting them. If our deliveries would be late, then I would assess delivery drivers and retrain them so they would effectively complete deliveries into a good manner. Same with the preparing of the orders, if this would take too long then chefs would be given retraining.

• Promoted to the Wandsworth shop because I have proved myself capable of managing an entire shop and have got a 5 stars Hygiene Rating.

Letting Negotiator/Marketing Manager at B&K Estates

September 2014

- Negotiated with clients ,answered calls.I would get clients everyday from the database and contact them and try to get approval for their rentals.Making over 100 calls a week.My biggest achievement was getting 10 properties in one day.
- Made ads to promote properties and managed viewings. Used company software to get the ads posted on
 different websites like Rightmove, Zoopla, company websites. Viewing were managed by me calling and confirming
 the viewing with the clients and the house owners, if needed to be rescheduled I would do that.

Receptionist at Berkley Court Hotel

July 2013

- Interacted with visitors and provided best customer service by getting them booked in and making sure the rooms were of high standards,and clean.
- Answered min 20 calls a day from manager and clients.
- Managing Booking system files.

Education

European Computer Driving Licence (ECDL)-ECDL certification
University Of Lower Danube -Chemistry of food products-Romania

July 2011